You catch anything?
Sorry, I didn't mean to
sneak up on you like that.
My name's Nishida, and I'm a fisherman.
In the game, anyway.
Back in Japan,
I was the head of network security for a
company called Toto High Speed Internet.
I'm Kirito.
Wait, wasn't Toto the company that... Yep.
We were the folks in charge of
network security for this game.
It's a big one!
Yeah, but I've cut bigger.
Whoa!
Awesome. Thanks.
I'm good at catching
them, but cooking them?
Yeah, not so good.
I'd love to make sashimi
or a nice stew out of them,
But what's the point when
I don't have any soy sauce?
I could go for fish baked with soy sauce
right now, or with radishes with soy sauce.
Hey, if you want, I just might be
able to help you out with that.
Wait, say what?
There's only one here, but I can't be.
I can't believe that I
can't believe in the world.
I can't believe that
I can't believe in it.
I have a small dream that
I've heard from all my life.
If I'm weak, if I'm you, I'll
be strong in the dark world.
I'll see my dreams forever.
I wanna always be waiting.
I'll give you everything I have.
Ah, that was an amazing meal.
I had no idea you could get
soy sauce in this world.
Actually, I made it myself.
If you want, you can
take some home with you.
Really?
Man, my taste buds bow down before you.
Glad you liked it.
By the way, how high
is your fishing skill?
I'm asking because Kirito hasn't
been able to catch anything yet.
Yeah, well, maybe if all the lakes
on this floor weren't so hard?
Well, actually, that's not true.
As far as fishing goes,
the only lake that's tough to catch anything
in is the big one you were at today!
What?
Why would someone design it like that?
Yes, good question!
That lake is the home of...
The king of all fish Seriously?
Yep, we're old pals
I've had him on the end of my hook
quite a few times, but he's so strong.
He yanks the pool right
out of my hands every time.
I Was wondering do you have
any plans for tomorrow?
Yeah, I Don't mind
helping the old guy out,
but how am I supposed to do a
switch move with a fishing pole?
You're the only one I
know who can figure it out
What if you catch it?
Will you keep it?
Is that even possible?
He is pretty cool,
though, don't you think?
When you both showed up, I
was like, who is this person?
Isn't it funny how people are
living normal lives in this world?
And since we're the
ones on the front lines,
their lives have sort of become
our responsibility, haven't they?
For me, I wasn't getting
stronger for anyone else.
It was just about me staying alive.
Everyone expects great
things from you now.
And guess what? So do I.
Talk about pressure, huh?
Yeah, I promised I'd save everyone.
Hell of a thing to live up to.
Oh, well.
They'll understand if you
take tonight off. Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Can you believe all the
people who showed up?
Well, here we go
Thanks for your patience everyone.
Here comes today's main event.
It's about time Kirito,
let's catch us a fish.
Yeah
How big this thing
supposed to be anyway, okay
Oh, ooh.
That was a scam, isn't it?
Live cameras there! I wanna fly!
Um...
shouldn't you reel it in?
No, not yet!
Uh... Nishida?
Hang on...
Not yet.
Now!
I got this sucker!
Here!
Uh, switch?
Call me here, you bastard!
Look!
It's coming up!
I think I tired him out.
Where are you going? Hey!
No, no, no, no!
Cait!
Look out!
For what?
You ran away!
You left me there to die!
Here it comes!
Whoa, we can run?
It's like a crazy lungfish. Kirito!
This is serious!
That thing's coming for us!
Hurry, do something!
Yeah, I'm still thinking.
Guess I'll take care of this.
Run while you still can!
Nah, she'll be fine.
Save your wife, Kirikou!
No! Watch out!
Oh, wow.
That was badass! Yes!
You're Asuna, right?
What are you doing here?
Man, this is Asuna.
I'm a big girl.
Can I see your hand?
Nice job, honey.
Heathcliff.
Come on.
You've moped long enough already.
I know, but it's only been two weeks.
If he needs us on the front lines,
then something must have happened.
Why else would he interrupt our vacation?
Yeah, but still.
Let's at least hear what he's got to say.
Come on, time to go.
We'll take care of this,
then come back. You got it.
Thanks for seeing us off.
I know we didn't get to spend much
time together, but it was fun.
Oh, well, it was an honor and a privilege.
Actually, before I met the two of you,
I couldn't imagine what the folks
working to clear the game were like.
You might as well have
been from another planet.
Being trapped in here
for the past two years,
even if I made it out alive, I don't
know if I can go back to my old job,
my old life.
Maybe deep down inside, I've
given up hope of ever getting out?
I figured spending my
time with a fishing pole
between my mitts was
the best thing for me!
Pretty sad, huh?
Uh-uh, that isn't sad.
I get what you mean.
I used to feel the same
as you, at first anyway.
I felt lost and hopeless.
Every night I'd cry myself to sleep.
It felt like each day that went by in here
was another day lost from my real life.
So I'd cry and afterwards I'd
go and fight as hard as I could.
All I cared about was winning.
Getting stronger and
getting to the next floor.
But then I was walking
along and I saw someone.
Taking a nap in the shade.
I was so mad I told him he
shouldn't waste his time like that.
And then he said, and
I'll never forget it.
This is Aincrad's best season and today's
weather is He said it's optimal setting.
He said it'd be a waste to go into
some dungeon on such a beautiful day.
So I tried lying down
too, and you know what?
I slept like a baby.
When I woke up, it was evening and
he was giving me the weirdest look.
Anyway, we formed our own party, and
that's when I realized something.
Even in a world like this,
he was really living.
He wasn't losing a day in the real world.
He was gaining a day. Here.
I learned so much from him.
And by him, I mean Kirito.
When I thought about him
before falling asleep,
I noticed I wouldn't have nightmares.
I began looking forward
to seeing him again.
It was like, for the first
time, I was glad I was here.
Kirito was everything to me.
He's what the last two years were about.
He's proof I'm alive.
Why'd I put on the nerve gear that day?
It's obvious so I could
come here and meet him.
You're still alive, right?
You must have something to live for, too.
Yeah, you're right.
Yeah, you're absolutely right.
Life isn't so bad here.
No, it's actually pretty.
I wish there was something I could
do to help, but well, there it is.
Good luck and be safe. Don't worry.
We'll go fishing again.
Take care, okay?
Teleport Gransom!
The recon team was wiped out?
They were scouting for
the upcoming boss fight.
It was a party of 20 members,
taken from five different guilds.
Ten of them reached
the center of the room.
Then the boss appeared.
And that's when the entrance closed,
cutting them off from the rest of the party.
They walked into an anti-crystal zone.
Precisely.
and it couldn't have been more than five
minutes or so when the door finally opened.
The room was empty.
There wasn't any trace left behind of the
ten soldiers, or the boss. You're kidding!
Now more than ever, clearing the game
should be everyone's number one priority.
We're going to launch an attack with
the largest group we can assemble.
You can count on us to fight with
you, but this needs to be clear.
Austin's safety is my priority.
If things start to get hairy in
there, I'm going to protect her.
That's not negotiable.
A person with something to
protect is a strong ally to have.
I'm expecting a good fight from you.
Three more hours of waiting.
What should we do?
What's wrong with you?
There's something I have to ask you.
But I don't want you getting mad at me.
Instead of going to the boss
fight, could you please stay here?
Why would you ask that?
We won't be able to use teleport crystals,
so there's no telling what could happen.
I'm scared.
If anything happened to you, I— So you
want to go to someplace dangerous, alone,
and you expect me to stay
here, where it's safe?
You know what would happen
if you didn't come back, huh?
I'd kill myself.
I'd never forgive myself for staying behind,
so what would be the point in living?
I'm sorry, I guess I'm losing my nerve.
All I want to do is run away with you.
I don't care if we never make
it back to the real world.
I just want to live with you.
in our little house in the woods.
It'd be nice if we could do that.
Be together, every day, forever.
Have you ever thought about what's
happening in the real world?
About what's happening to our
bodies while we're in here?
A few weeks after the game was
launched, do you remember what happened?
Most of the players suddenly went offline
and stayed that way for a few hours.
My guess is that's when
all the players' bodies
were being moved to
hospitals in the real world.
If that's where we all are right
now in hospitals barely being kept
alive by machines it's hard to believe
we're going to survive like that
for much longer so that means it
doesn't matter whether we clear the
game or not anymore everyone here is
on a time limit and once that's up?
I…
I want to…
to stay with you forever.
I want us to go on real dates.
And to really get married.
And for us to grow old together.
That's why…
that's why…
We don't have a choice.
We have to keep fighting.
Hey!
No way.
You guys are coming too?
That's the best you got?
No way?
Hey, man, I shut my shop down to
come out here and help get this done.
Brother, you're looking at a player who's
about as philanthropic as they come.
Then seeing as how
you're so philanthropic,
you're not gonna mind if we
take you off the drop list.
Well, hey now, let's
not be too hasty, man.
Corridor, open.
Well, here we go.
Feel that?
There's a bad vibe in here. Yeah.
Everyone ready?
The Knights of the Blood
Oath will be out in front
distracting the boss and
blocking its attacks.
In the meantime the
rest of you have to stay
sharp and try to figure
out its attack patterns.
I won't lie this battle will be hard but
I have faith that we can and will prevail.
For our day of liberation.
Everything's gonna be
fine I won't let anything
happen to you promise
make sure you protect me.
Too okay yeah you know I will.
Don't die guys same to you buddy I'm
gonna make a fortune off today's drops.
No way am I missing out on that.
Forward to battle!
Nothing's happening. Where is it?
Up there!
It's the skull. Reaper.
Stay away from it! Red up!
This way!
Hurry, run!
That was one hit.
Man, we are so dead.
You can't even get in close
enough to hit the damn thing!
Look out!
It's too strong!
If we block it together, we have a chance.
Come on, we can do this! Okay.
Me and Oxenel, deal with the signs!
Everyone else, flank it and attack!
You heard the man! Okay!
Hold still, baby!
Damn you!
Ready, Kirito? Yeah!
Ah! Ah! Oh!
I heard a little bit of a song.
It's just a little lonely.
Maybe I'll be strong!
I'll be high.
I'll be high!
But the reality is that the reality is?
The dreams of the stars.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
Next time, the end of the world.